Antonio Martinez

antonios.martinez.dev@gmail.com +506 6017 0413 Heredia, Costa Rica https://martinezantonio.github.io/

Summary

+7 years of professional career as a Full Stack Web Developer, participating in the product development of successful web applications.

Good understanding of OOP programming and MVC pattern design. Excellent debugging skills and good webmaster concepts.

Good understanding of web services and SOA-related standards like REST / OAuth / JSON.

A day in my life may consist of: Design a responsive landing page in HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap, develop a custom plugin in WordPress, adding an API Rest endpoint, MySQL database design, read the documentation of new PHP releases, fix some jQuery conflicts or JavaScript bugs, back up websites, programming some component or service in angular CLI, and some more cool stuff.

Experience

Web Developer

Jazz Gaming Solutions • San Jose, Costa Rica

01/2018 - 09/2020

I was responsible for developing, implementing and maintaining mostly internal web applications. I collaborated with technical and business staff in the design, development, testing, implementation and production support of enterprise applications in PHP and Angular CLI.

We primarily used MEAN Stack. 40% of my work was doing front end development, 40% back end development and the remaining 20% was dev-ops/sys admin related tasks.

Web Developer

PROFI • San Jose, Costa Rica

04/2014 - 02/2017

At PROFI, I was working on PHP, WordPress, Javascript (Angular CLI and vanilla).

Some of my web apps included: Custom WordPress plugins and widgets, digital menu boards, mobile/desktop business dashboards, online website plugins, and APIs integrations. I was also responsible for managing my team's web infrastructure, SEO, marketing, and website design.

I also developed a hotel reservation system built in PHP and uses MySQL to store data.

The script provides a powerful room booking and reservation management functionality.

Web Developer

CIP Reporting • Virginia, United States

08/2016 - 06/2017

At my current position, I am working on a large reporting system for casinos. Giving them maintenance and programming new reports and new functions. We use technologies such as PHP 5.3v, MySQL databases, jQuery, CSS, and AJAX.

In addition to full-stack development, I also working on a lot of dev-ops tasks. I have helped set up a lot of our unit, UI, and build/deploy plans.

Email templates design in HTML and CSS. SMTP and mailPHP email templates sending.

Web Developer

Netsoft • San Jose, Costa Rica

03/2013 - 02/2014

When I was 18, my first job was at NETSOFT.

Programming and maintaining ERP systems. One of them was Dolibarr, a very robust open-source made in PHP and MySQL. I did some things like, develop new reports, migrate and export data in JSON and XML format, modify MySQL databases, SMTP emails, design templates with HTML and CSS, among some other things.

Technologies

- PHP
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML5
- Sass

- MySQL
- Angular
- JQuery
- Git
- Bootstrap

Education

High school

Liceo Ingeniero Manuel Benavides Rodriguez • San Jose, Costa Rica Currently completing courses in computer science, robotics and statistics 02/2015

Languages

· Spanish

· English

Projects

https://mybookie.ag

https://xbet.ag

https://martinezantonio.github.io

https://plive.ganchrow.com

https://www.cipreporting.com

https://jazzsports.ag

https://scoresandodds.com

https://toyotacr.com

https://stayincostarica.com

https://tabacon.com

https://guachipelin.com

https://bestwesterjacobeach.com

PHP LinkedIn Assessments



Great work! You earned a badge.

You're in the top 5% of 315k people who took this PHP LinkedIn Assessments



Antonio

Web developer

PHP



LinkedIn Skill Assessment badge